communispace.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy – English | C Space

### Privacy Policy

Communispace Corporation d/b/a C Space and Promise Corporation Limited t/a C Space (collectively, “C Space” or “we”) is committed to respecting your privacy and will only use your personal information for market research purposes. This Privacy Policy explains how C Space treats your personal information obtained through your use of the C Space website (the “Site”) and/or online market research communities hosted and conducted by C Space (a “Community”).

**_Topics:_**

  * Who we are
  * What personal information we collect
  * When and how we collect your personal information
  * How we use your personal information
  * How we protect your information
  * How long we keep your personal information
  * Accessing hyperlinks and other websites
  * Use of the C Space mobile application
  * Special information of California residents
  * Data originating from the European Economic Area (EEA)
    * The legal basis for using European personal information
    * Processing your information outside the EEA
    * Dispute resolution
    * Who we share your information with
  * How we collect and use information about children
  * Your choices and rights
  * Rights for EEA Residents
  * Questions or feedback

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this Site. If we make material changes to this policy, we will give you notice of such changes by posting the revised policy on this Site, and where appropriate, by other means. This policy was last updated on April 30, 2018.

#### Who We Are

Promise Corporation Limited t/a C Space is a wholly owned subsidiary of Communispace Corporation d/b/a C Space. Promise Corporation Limited and Communispace Corporation are collectively referred to in this policy as “C Space.” C Space is a leading provider of market research services. Our services include conducting online market research projects (“Communities”) on behalf of our clients (“Sponsor”) as well as providing downloadable market research insights and information through our Site.

#### What Personal Information We Collect

The information we collect on our Site and through Communities generally falls into the following two categories: Personal Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Personal Information refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Non-Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. If we do combine Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Personal Information, the combined information will be treated as Personal Information for as long as it remains combined.

In general, we collect Personal Information about you through our Site related to your identity and contact information such as your name, e-mail address, company name, job title and company address. If you participate in our Communities, we may collect additional Personal Information about you, such as your date of birth, home address, phone number, online user identity (ex. social media accounts), marital status and family details. We may also collect limited amounts of Sensitive Data, such as health information, through certain Communities.

Other data may be collected automatically through the website (such as IP addresses, browser characteristics, device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, information on actions taken on our website, and dates and times of website visits).  

#### When and How We Collect Your Personal Information

In general, we collect your Personal Information when you voluntarily provide it on our Site and through our Communities. When you provide Personal Information to us, we may ask if you want to receive future marketing information and communication from us, such as newsletters, email or other information. You can choose not to receive this communication, if you wish. If you have already chosen to receive such communication, you can ask us to stop by clicking the opt-out link on any email communication, or by emailing a request to [privacy@cspace.com](mailto:privacy@cspace.com). C Space may also obtain Personal Information from trusted vendors who have previously obtained information and appropriate permission and consent from you.

In addition, our Site may use “cookies” to gather Non-Personally Identifiable Information. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to store information, such as your email address, username and/or password, about your preferences and activity during and after your visit to a website. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually refuse cookies, or selectively accept certain cookies, by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, there may be some features and functions of our Site and Communities that will not be available to you and some pages may not display properly.

We may use the following types of Cookies within our Site and our mobile applications:

1\. _Strictly necessary cookies_ – “Strictly Necessary” cookies are required for the operation of the Site. These cookies let you access and navigate the Community and allow you to use essential features and secure areas. Without these cookies, services you have asked for cannot be provided. Please note that we do not use information gathered from these cookies for marketing purposes or for remembering where you’ve been on the internet.

2\. _Analytics cookies_ – These cookies allow us to track and analyze page visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our Site using a service provided by Google Analytics. They allow us to collect statistical information about our visitors, such as whether they have visited the Site before and the pages they view. This information is gathered anonymously; it does not enable us to identify who you are and we do not combine any analytic information we collect from these cookies with your personally identifiable information.

3\. _Preference cookies_ – These cookies may be used to save your personal preferences so that we can remember your settings and display personalized information to you the next time you visit. Generally, these types of cookies require you to “opt in” to store your preference.

4\. _Session cookies_ – These cookies store temporary information to enable Site functionality. They are automatically deleted when you close your browser.

5\. _Third Party cookies_ – These cookies may be set on our Site by other companies or “third parties”. These companies may collect data that enables them to display advertisements on other sites that are relevant to your interests or these cookies may be used to allow for functionality of third party applications or devices we offer on our Site. For more information on these cookies, please visit the relevant third-party website.

#### How We Use Your Personal Information

_Information Collected Through our Site_ : Personal Information you provide through C Space’s Site is used to provide you with email updates and marketing communications from us about our services, such as newsletters or emails. Your information may also be used to help us track the way you use our Site and our products. We may also combine the information you provide with information that we collect separately, including information you have provided to other organizations (with consent that it can be shared) as well as public information. All of this information will help us to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services.

_Information Collected Through our Communities_ : Personal Information you provide through C Space’s Communities is used for market research purposes, such as:  
a. to determine whether you meet the criteria for a “Community;”  
b. to communicate with you regarding C Space’s services and/or your participation in a Community;  
c. for market research conducted on behalf of a C Space client;  
d. to analyze, evaluate and/or improve C Space’s Site, services and/or market research tools.

We will not use Personal Information collected through Communities for direct marketing purposes (however, if you have provided your information to C Space in other ways, such as through our Site, we may use your information to contact you as set forth above).

In some circumstances, the information you provide may include Sensitive Data (ethnicity, income, education, etc.). C Space collects such Sensitive Data solely for meeting the market research goals of C Space and the Sponsor. Specifically, collecting this Sensitive Data allows C Space and the Sponsor to create a balanced community reflective of a certain consumer population or its segments. Such information is not collected for any discriminatory purposes. You will always retain the right not to answer any question with which you do not feel comfortable.

#### How We Protect Your Information

We use reasonable and appropriate technological and physical safeguards to protect Personal Information you provide to us from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in the processing and the nature of the Personal Information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. In order to ensure that your information is protected when transferred out of the EEA, C Space relies on inter-company agreements between our various affiliates that may process your information on behalf of C Space. If you would like a copy of these agreements, please email us at [privacy@cspace.com](mailto:privacy@cspace.com).

#### How Long We Keep Your Personal Information

In general, we will only retain your information for the time necessary to realize our legitimate business purposes and to comply with the law. However, we may continue to store anonymous or anonymized information, such as Site visits, without identifiers, in order to improve our services.

#### Accessing Hyperlinks and Other Website

Our Site and/or Communities may interface with third party sites and services, (for example, Facebook® or other third party applications or services) or contain links to websites operated by others. This Privacy Policy only applies to C Space’s Site and Communities. Privacy policies for these third party sites and services may be different from our privacy policy. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site or integrated service before disclosing any personal information on such site and/or through such service. C Space is not responsible for information you submit to third parties.

Currently, to help facilitate login to our communities, we may offer in some Communities, at the Sponsor’s discretion, a sign-on service that allows you to sign into your Community using login credentials from your Facebook® account. This allows you to associate your existing Facebook® profile with your C Space account. By linking these accounts, C Space will have access to certain profile information contained within your Facebook® profile such as your full name, email, locale, gender, profile picture, as well as other publicly available profile information. No Community content will ever be shared on Facebook® without your express permission. You can disassociate your Facebook® account from your Community account at any time by clicking “Unlink” on your Member Profile page.

#### Use of the C Space Mobile Application

In some Communities, members may have the option to participate in Community activities on their mobile device through C Space’s mobile application. Use of the mobile application is voluntary and optional. Members who choose to use the mobile application must provide their Community login and password to access and complete mobile Community activities. The mobile application may request your permission to collect location data and/or may request access to multimedia stored on your mobile device (i.e. photos or videos). Location data is not required for participation in Community activities; if you do not wish for your location data to be submitted, please respond accordingly when prompted on your mobile device. Multimedia will only be collected from your device if you affirmatively select it for submission through the application (i.e. you chose an image or video to submit for a Community activity). You can change your permissions with respect to location data and multimedia sharing through the settings feature on your mobile device. Any information and content collected through the mobile application will be used consistent with this Policy and the policies and agreements applicable to your Community.

Use of the mobile application may not be available in all Communities, at the Sponsor’s discretion.

#### Special Information for California Consumers

California residents may request a list of certain third parties to which we have disclosed personally identifiable information about you for their own direct marketing purposes. You may make one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response. You may request this information in writing by reaching us at the contact points below. Please allow up to thirty (30) days for a response.

#### Data Originating from the European Economic Area (EEA)

_The Legal Basis for Using European Personal Information_  
When we collect information about you through our Site, the legal basis on which we process your Personal Information is our legitimate interests, namely, to provide you with information marketing our technology and services.

When we collect information about you through our Communities, the legal basis on which we process your Personal Information is the performance of our contract with you to participate in our Communities. If we collect any information about you through our Communities and process it in a way that is not necessary for our performance of our contract with you, the legal basis on which we will process your Personal Information will be your consent.

_Storage and Processing of Personal Information Outside the EEA_  
If you are located in the EEA, your Personal Information is processed by C Space’s EU based affiliate, Promise. Please note that as part of our service, we may transfer your personal information to other regions, including to the United States.

C Space complies with the US Department of Commerce EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield program regarding the transfer of Personal Information from European Union member countries and Switzerland to the United States. C Space has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is a conflict between our Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield, Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.

To learn more about the Privacy Shield Program and to view our certification, please visit: [privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome).

#### _Dispute Resolution_

C Space has mechanisms in place designed to help assure compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles. C Space conducts an annual self-assessment of its Personal Information practices to verify that the attestations and assertions C Space makes about its Privacy Shield privacy practices are true and that C Space’s privacy practices have been implemented as represented and in accordance with the Privacy Shield Principles.

You may file a complaint concerning C Space’s processing of your Personal Information. C Space will take steps to remedy issues arising out of its alleged failure to comply with the Privacy Shield Principles. You may contact C Space as specified below about complaints regarding C Space’s Personal Information practices.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, C Space commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your Personal Information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact C Space at [privacy@cspace.com](mailto:privacy@cspace.com).

C Space has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States, under the JAMS EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you. For more information and/or to file a complaint, please visit: [jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield](https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield). C Space is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) to ensure compliance with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield principles outlined in this policy.

If your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.

#### _Who We Share Your Information With_

C Space shares Personal Information with its affiliates and subsidiaries. We may also share your information with companies who carry out work for us. C Space requires these companies to agree to:  
a. only process the Personal Information for limited and specified purposes consistent with your consent;  
b. provide the same level of protection for Personal Information as is required by the Privacy Shield Principles; and  
c. notify C Space and cease processing Personal Information (or take other reasonable and appropriate remedial steps) if the company determines that it cannot meet its obligation to provide the same level of protection for Personal Information as is required by the Privacy Shield Principles.

We do not share the information you provide with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure.

If you participate in C Space’s Communities, we may share your information with the Sponsor for whom the market research is conducted. In most cases, your information is shared with Community Sponsors only on an aggregate and anonymous basis. In some cases, however, C Space may share your Personal Information with the Community Sponsor or the Sponsor may have access to that information in the Community. In these circumstances, your Personal Information may be handled in accordance with the Sponsor’s privacy policy, a copy of which will be made available through your Community, but the Sponsor’s use of your information will also be consistent with the purposes set forth above.

Other than as set forth above, we may use and/or disclose your information, including your Personal Information, to enforce, and/or investigate violations of, our site Terms of Use, a Community Member Agreement, and/or this Policy. Although unlikely, your Personal Information may also be disclosed to the governments, courts, law enforcement or regulatory agencies under a lawful order in a jurisdiction where you are located and/or where your Personal Information is stored and/or processed. You cannot opt out of disclosure of your Personal Information if required by lawful order.

#### How We May Collect and Use Information About Children

C Space’s Site is not intended for use by children, particularly those under age 16, and we do not knowingly collect information from children. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information on the Site from a child under age 16, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under 16, please contact us at [privacy@cspace.com.](mailto:privacy@cspace.com)

We do, however, collect information about children under the age of 16 from their parents through some of our Communities. We ask that our users do not provide information about a child without first obtaining consent from the child’s parents. Where appropriate, we will always ask for consent from a parent or guardian to collect information about children. In the event that we learn we have collected any Personal Information from a child under the age of 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as possible.

#### Your Choices and Rights

You have several choices regarding the use and disclosure of your information.

_Information You Provide_ : With respect to the collection of your information, if you do not want your Personal Information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted information and would like to review, correct or remove it from our records, please contact your community facilitator or [privacy@cspace.com](mailto:privacy@cspace.com).

_Cookies_ : If you wish to disable cookies, you can set your browser not to accept cookies. You can find out how to do so here: [aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/). Please note though that if you turn off cookies, there may be some features and functions of our Site that will not be available to you and some pages may not display properly

_Information Shared with Third Parties_ : You may also choose whether your Personal Information may be disclosed to third-parties or used for a purpose that is materially different from the purposes for which the information was originally collected or subsequently authorised by you. To the extent required by the Privacy Shield Principles, C Space obtains opt-in consent for certain uses and disclosures of Sensitive Data. You may contact C Space as indicated below regarding the company’s use or disclosure of your Personal Information. Unless C Space offers you an appropriate choice, we use Personal Information only for purposes that are materially the same as those indicated in this Policy.

#### Rights for EEA Residents

In addition, if you are a resident of the EEA, you have the right to:  
• Find out if we use your Personal Information, to access your Personal Information, and receive copies of your Personal Information.  
• Withdraw your consent to the processing of your Personal Information at any time without penalty.  
• Access your Personal Information and have it corrected or amended if it is inaccurate or incomplete.  
• Obtain a transferable copy of some of your Personal Information which can be transferred to another provider when the Personal Information was processed based on your consent.  
• If you believe your Personal Information is inaccurate, unlawful, no longer necessary for our business purposes, or if you object to our processing of your Personal Information, you also have the right to instruct us to restrict the processing of your data pending our investigation and/or verification of your claim.  
• Request your Personal Information be deleted or restricted under certain circumstances. For example, if C Space is using your Personal Information on the basis of your consent and has no other legal basis to use such, you may request your Personal Information be deleted when you withdraw your consent.  
If you wish to exercise any of these rights, or raise a complaint on how we have handled your Personal Information, please contact us at [privacy@cspace.com](mailto:privacy@cspace.com).  
If you are not satisfied with our response, or believe we are processing your Personal Information in violation of the law, you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office [ico.org.uk](https://ico.org.uk/)

#### Questions or Feedback

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy and practice, please email us at [privacy@cspace.com](mailto:privacy@cspace.com) or by using the contact details below:
